Three figures walk across a barren, foggy wasteland. Massive, jagged stone shards jut from the earth.
A bare foot steps forward, the leg tightly wrapped in maroon leather. The three figures stand before a towering rock face, where an ornate metallic door seals a massive cave entrance.
Seen from behind, a figure holding a staff watches as the heavy metallic doors slide open, revealing a bright white light.
Ornate gold bracers cover a pair of crossed arms over dark red robes. Inside the cavern, the three figures walk down a narrow bridge toward a glowing structure rooted in the darkness.
They look up at a massive, dark shrine, where a figure stands suspended.
Golden energy swirls around the figure's metallic face and high, pointed headdress.
A blinding burst of light strikes a central pillar, surging outward along twisting, root-like tendrils to illuminate circular nodes.
Three armored figures emerge from the glare. The central figure wears a dark cape, their featureless face a mask of glowing energy.
A towering, intricate spire rises into the darkness. A solitary figure stands in a golden, illuminated alcove at its base.
Sleek ships fly over a pale landscape.
Bright green geometric lines illuminate the depths of the trench. Everything fades to black.